<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>org.unofficialrevport.REVHubInterface</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">org.unofficialrevport.REVHubInterface.desktop</launchable>
    <name>REV Hub Interface - Community Edition</name>
    <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
    <project_license>BSD-3-Clause</project_license>
    <summary>Directly control a REV Robotics Expansion Hub</summary>
    <description>The REV Hub Interface is a piece of software allowing for a direct connection from a REV Expansion Hub and its peripherals to a PC.

This interface provides a method for teams to prototype with motors, servos, and sensors in a way that is faster and easier than setting up an entire robot control system. It is also a valuable troubleshooting tool that can help isolate the cause of an issue and determine if it is electrical or software related. The REV Hub Firmware can also be updated and recovered through this interface in addition to the Robot Controller Application.

This is a community continuation of the software, updating to newer underlying technologies (e.g. porting from Python 2 to Python 3), adding features, and porting to more platforms (Linux and macOS, in addition to Windows). Though initially created by REV, this version of the software is not maintained by or affiliated with REV. Do not contact REV support about any issues you experience with this software, instead you may create a GitHub Issue at https://github.com/unofficial-rev-port/REVHubInterface/ or ask in https://discord.gg/pU2fesSTqF.
    </description>
    <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/unofficial-rev-port/REVHubInterface/</url>
    <url type="contact">https://discord.gg/pU2fesSTqF</url>
    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/unofficial-rev-port/REVHubInterface/</url>
    <developer id="org.unofficialrevport">
        <name>The Unofficial REV Port Team</name>
        <url>https://unofficialrevport.org</url>
    </developer>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />

</component>